You must drink a lot in the palace.
It's just that after work,
I'll drink a little when I get home.
After all, I often have missions.
Women and wine.
Among the army and Navy,
are indispensable.
Actually,
I'm on a mission.
Drinking is against the rules.
But Captain Oshima is so generous.
If I don't drink it,
if I don't drink.
So I'll make an exception today.
I'm so stupid.
But we're at Airlines 6.
It's okay to drink some.
His Majesty's personal guard.
It must be very mysterious.
Can you tell us about the palace?
Especially the guards
who have unique skills.
Colonel.
Inaki.
He grew up in China.
He doesn’t know much about Japan.
Colonel, can you talk to him?
Please.
They won't tell anyone.
Right?
His Majesty's personal guard
is a group of nine.
I'm not included.
What is your main task
your main mission?
Our mission
is to ensure
their loyalty to His Majesty.
Not only do they work and live,
and everything outside,
are in our surveillance at any time.
So
the palace investigators often go out.
It's really rare
to go out like this.
So for the Navy and the Army,
those adults
need your help.
It's easy for us
it's easy for us
to meet some big shots.
But we won't use them.
In our Chief Guard's words,
if the Navy or Army
the Navy or the Army,
What a joke!
Unbelievable.
I see.
What do you mean?
In fact, we're just shield of survival.
At the same time,
some secrets.
For someone,
we are also hidden dangers.
We've met too many people.
in front of His Majesty.
[Flirting]
and sow discord.
Of course they don't want
to be remembered by others.
Really?
That's enough.
It's going to be leaked.
Cheers.
By the way,
Irigami.
Bring me the best wine.
There's no good wine.
That's it.
There is.
I'll get it right away.
Wait for me.
There's good wine.
Let me do it.
Here's the wine.
Please.
Colonel.
Hot wine.
Don't miss it.
Only three drinks.
This is the rules of the Servant Room Iron.
You work outside.
Don't mind the rules in the palace.
Fukuda.
You're here.
Do you have beer?
Yes.
Please get me a bottle.
Right away.
In order not to disappoint you,
I'll have some beer with you.
This bottle of wine...
for me.
I can't drink much.
I’d better buy it to you.
Please.
I dare not drink for you.
I heard that Oshima-san can drink a lot.
I really want to see it.
It'll get cold if you push more.
Let Mr. Akino decide.
I think this bottle of wine
should be returned to its owner.
Colonel.
Please.
If you keep delaying it,
I can only think that
people from your palace
look down on
basic soldiers.
All these years,
I've been serving His Majesty
and serve him.
It's rare to get out.
This time,
although
such a remote place,
But I saw
Everyone here
for His Majesty.
I was very excited.
Please allow me to take the initiative.
Cheers.
Thank you so much.
Fukuda.
Don't be shy.
We are
who are loyal to His Majesty.
Thank you.
Colonel.
Here.
Okay.
Please.
For Your Majesty.
For the Empire of Japan!
Cheers!
Cheers.
Mr. Ye,
I'll say it again.
Our country is in danger.
We must cooperate.
What do you think?
Let's work together.
If you need anything,
we’ll try our best
and Macau Station.
Let's protect the people on the island
and Miss Ye's father.
ask you
Can we use
Can we use it?
No problem.
I think this will work.
Fatt
Come on.
Here's to you.
Thank you.
Mr. Ye.
I have a letter
to the island tonight.
Can I use it?
No problem.
Leave it to me.
Father.
I'm sorry.
I didn't become
a real samurai.
have no courage to go to the battlefield.
I can only stay here
here.
Let me tell you something.
The wine you drink
have been mixed with water.
Many foods are expired
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
Calm down.
Colonel is here.
You must be tired.
Let’s end it here.
Good night.
It's okay.
I think everyone is happy.
But indeed,
It's getting late tonight.
I’m almost done.
Colonel, please.
You can’t leave.
Colonel.
You can’t go back now.
Our leader
have something to tell you.
The leader has always been suspicious.
What's wrong?
What happened?
Come on.
Let's continue drinking.
Drink!
Oshima-san!
Thank you for the dinner.
Thank you for coming.
Drunk is divided into two situations.
One is drunk harassment type.
and the other is sober.
Captain Akino should be the last one.
It's just that his legs aren't working well.
By the way,
I have a favor to ask.
Can you use your car?
to send Captain Akino
to the base dorm.
OK.
Colonel.
Aren’t you going back to the airport?
Yes.
There are some things
a witness hasn't finished yet.
It's late.
Forget about today.
The habit of being in the attendant room for years.
What happened today must end today.
Please.
All right.
Take Mr. Akino to the car.
I'm with Commander.
I'm watching you.
Commander...
Stop it.
Get him into the car.
Yes.
Long live the Emperor!
Oshima-san, I'll get going too.
Goodbye.
Come here.
Ask the well to come out.
Yes.
How's the Major?
I just changed his dressing.
Can you walk?
Is the gauze ready?
Yes.
What about Dragon Hero?
He's waiting at the beach.
Ju is also in the hospital.
Okay.
I'll go to the hospital now.
Wait for me here.
I'll come back to pick you up.
After you go to the hospital,
let's play it by ear.
I'm leaving.
Be careful.
Okay.
You are a second-class soldier of the airport garrison.
Leiji?
What's wrong with him?
He can't talk because his skull is injured.
I see.
I'm an investigator from Tokyo.
I'm Ichiro Takemichi.
I have some questions for you.
If it's you, nod
If it's not you, shake your head.
Okay?
I need you to recall
On February 3, 4 last year,
the special plane of General Kokuri
During daily maintenance and maintenance
maintenance and maintenance,
you were one of the flight attendants.
right?
That's good.
I need to ask you
to ask you in detail.
Can you take a car?
Are you the nurse who takes care of him?
Yes.
I need to take him out.
It'll take about half an hour.
You take care of him.
Is there a problem?
Yes.
Go get a wheelchair.
Carry him into the car.
Yes.
Ah.
What?
What did you say?
I don't understand.
You want to go back to the hospital?
Okay.
I'll send you back right away.
I'll take you home.
Hold him tight.
I knocked him out.
Can you handle it well?
Make it clean.
Remember to keep your clothes.
Bye.
Take care.
Ju.
Take it.
Tell him when you get to hell.
I sent you here
sent you here.
Sir.
I've finished
Done.
Please take a look.
Not bad.
You have to work harder.
and send this plan
to Commander Fujita.
Do I need your approval?
He won't.
The Navy's general...
...is to take responsibility.
We just need to
the plan.
Yes.
Thank you.
This is
on April 12th.
The captain asked me
to give it to you in person.
I know.
Oshima Hao called just now.
I mean...
Are you sure you want to do this?
Yes.
Habha!
If you get rid of
on the island,
It's safe.
The Navy and Navy
the Navy and Navy navigators.
Have you done an evaluation?
Captain Oshima asked us
to contact the Tuo Minister.
and request for
as soon as possible.
How many people
How many immigrants?
Get ready soon.
Prepare to move from Okinawa
from Okinawa.
That's a big deal.
How many copies have you printed?
Just one.
Captain Oshima asked us
to give orders
will be given verbal orders.
You may leave.
I’m leaving.
General, it's time for your medicine.
Habha!
A investigator from Tokyo.
We're investigating today.
the sentry soldiers who worked for General Tai Kok last year.
And...
the airport guards and the Special Forces Police Brigade
All the participants
were asked to question.
Okay.
Do you need me to keep the documents?
No.
I can do it myself.
I'll take my leave.
Fujita is introverted and sharp.
I can tell
the purpose of the Special Forces Police Brigade.
But
he would never
sign his name
on this document.
He doesn't want to take the responsibility.
Stay in the car.
Don't move.
Fukuda.
Colonel.
It’s late.
Why are you still here?
I'm with my woman.
shouldn't you stay away from me?
Not to get closer.
With all due respect,
why do you put a Chinese woman
by your side?
Japanese women are 100 times better than her.
If you need,
I can introduce you anytime.
The best in my place.
What are you talking about?
I'm tired.
Go back.
Shut up!
You ugly woman.
It's none of your business
is none of your business.
I'm sorry.
Move.
Yes.
Please.
Heavy 08596.
Slow down.
Do you think that Yankee
is still hiding somewhere?
Well...
It's such a big island.
To be honest,
I've searched everywhere.
I found his hideout,
but I couldn't find him.
Where else could he be hiding?
I think so too.
I lost my goal.
Don't panic.
Just keep an eye on
our suspects.
will find him soon.
The colonel is driving our car.
We can't keep an eye on him.
Yeah.
We can't follow them
follow them.
We need to take the initiative.
Sasaki.
Yes.
After breakfast,
Go and get Fukuda
and the maintenance meeting.
His name is Tang Bingchen.
Bring them here.
I need to explain to them
the plan I told you yesterday.
Okay.
I’ll go after eating.
Captain.
What was it called?
This is
killing two birds with one stone.
No.
It should be killing three birds with one stone.
The key point of this plan is...
Inaki.
By then,
take a patrol boat
with a fishing boat.
In this way,
to make the fishermen feel at ease
and make the Macao people feel
we're not on guard.
Also,
that Yankee hiding in the dark
might be waiting for the chance to move out.
4 p.m.
gather all fishing boats.
At 4:30,
I'm in Hengqin Island.
I led the other four patrol boats
to this sea.
It's estimated that
The mafia in Macau
and Jiang Zheng Quan's boats
It's time to show up.
and catch them all.
That way,
the unstable young men
on the island.
And
we can catch the Yankees.
This is killing three birds with one stone.
That's brilliant.
Sasaki.
Find out what happened yesterday.
where
with that woman?
Got it.
Xia.
I have news.
Two letters.
Big Tiger and Little Tiger have been lost.
Don't be anxious.
I will negotiate with the chiefs
and come up with another plan.
Cut.
Please give the other letter to Ying'er.
There's no word
It's for Ying Er
Ying Er
Ying Er.
Dad.
What's the rush?
This is a letter from your uncle.
He said it's for you.
For me?
It should be for Takemichi.
I'll send it to him.
Mr. Tang.
Okay.
Thank you.
Captain Oshima.
So early?
so early.
Is there
something urgent?
It's the end of April.
is the Emperor's birthday.
The Marines
the Navy will prepare for a celebration.
This year,
we plan to lift the sea ban
and organize all young fishermen
to conduct a fishing activity.
We hope
we can verify
the list of capturing people going to sea.
As for the specific time,
the police force will inform you.
That is to say,
We can sail!
If the villagers know this good news,
they will
thank you, Captain Oshima.
That's right.
Old people and young children
Soldiers and ordinary citizens
Everyone
should celebrate for His Majesty.
Go back and tell everyone.
to prepare for the fishing.
Then...
[The fish we caught this time is Fukuda Trade Bank.]
Fukuda Trading
will purchase everything
according to the market price.
Okay.
I'll tell the villagers
to the villagers.
Chairman Tang.
The fishing boat and staff
must be registered.
Let Fukuda
take someone and maintenance to do it together.
Good job.
Did Sasaki tell you? Yes.
Yes.
You have to go to every family.
Understood.
All the young men on the island
will be listed on this sail list.
One more thing.
Secret investigation.
Who's keeping pigeons?
Pigeon?
Keep it a secret.
Don't let too many people know.
Yes.
When the list is ready,
let me know right away.
Fukuda will go with you.
Okay.
Captain.
Did you find anything?
They went to the military hospital yesterday.
Military hospital.
Captain.
What’s the hurry?
Captain, we stay
in the cave
We found this at the corner of the dandelion grass.
To the military hospital.
We found a lot of doubts on Mount Mudang.
Takemuki came to the military hospital yesterday.
Why did he come to the military hospital?
What's the connection?
Great.
Your fever is gone.
Thank you.
After a few more days,
the inflammation should be gone.
What medicine is this?
Penicillin.
Has there been
at the base hospital recently?
No.
Absolutely not.
Are you sure?
Captain Oshima.
Although this medicine is penicillin,
but I'm not sure
it was from our hospital.
You are the only hospital in the base.
All teams have this medicine.
Anyway, I can guarantee
this medicine
in our hospital.
It will never happen.
lost.
You've been in the hospital these days?
Yes.
Is there anyone suspicious?
No.
Did Colonel Takemuki and his woman
come here?
Yes.
What are you doing here?
Colonel came to prescribe some medicine.
That woman
almost had a conflict
with a patient.
Be specific.
A patient
was harsh to Nurse Tang.
In order to protect her,
she seems to know some medical skills.
How do you know?
She said some medical terms.
But his assistant
It's normal to speak some medical terms.
What medicine did Colonel prescribe?
Colonel is an old TB.
and prescribed some medicine for his lungs.
Do you have this medicine?
No.
It's getting interesting.
Do you trust this doctor?
The Penicillin incident
is a lie.
But about the Colonel we talked about later,
He doesn’t need to protect him.
Tell him
we're here to ask him today.
about our questioning today.
What should we do next?
Of course.
to see the colonel's woman.
of the Colonel woman.
Oshima Hao.
Oshimahao is here.
What's wrong?
Oshima Hao is here.
Oshima Hao
Who is it?
Captain of the Police Brigade on the island.
Don't panic.
Just do what you usually do.
He won't come in.
Remember,
You can't talk.
Let's take a look.
This is...
The one who was broken by the villagers.
Private?
Private second class Yang
Hey.
Let me ask you something.
Captain Oshima!
His pelvis
was injured by the villagers using hoes.
I can't talk.
A pelvis.
Actor table.
Oshima Hao Wooden (Japan)
Wei, Chen, Shao, Tong,
Luo Zhiyong, Liao Wangwang.
Sasaki, Middle Spring Hero (Japan)
Commander Fujita, Kobayashi Chengnan (Japan)
Dr. Jin, Ouyang Wangjia.
Halong, Chen Weixu.
Akashi, Songpo.
Rat Zhao Shuai.
Yumiko Liu Yi.
Inabe Akira Senbo (Japan)
Stupid Ho Zhi Long.
Lieutenant Li, Zhang Zhizhong.
Yau Gang Wang Zheng.
[Yohei Matsukaku]
Shoichi Kimura
Yamamoto 56, Kenichi Miura (Japan)
Leiji Jiang Kun
Mr. Chen, Luo Shiping.
Chen, An, Gao Haishan.
Director Wang, Chen Xuming.
Commissioner Yan, Huang Wenhao.
Li Jingfeng from Chenqiao.
Bingyi, Yue Junling.
Captain Zhong, Zhou Jie.
Da Hu, Zhang Jun.
Tiger, Jin Guangzheng.
Yuan and Ma Yan.
Master Qin, Zhao Haiying.
Cigarette girl Yu Li
Qing, Mu, Liu Fenggu.
Ye, Tian, Feng, Falls.
Yang Cheng Ming from Nagano.
Secretary Zhao, Shi Yifu.
Zheng Cai Fu, Chen Jun.
Xu Shengsheng, Xue Conghai, Zhang Xiaolei, Xiao Zhenyang, Li, Yu, Liu Haibo, Zhu Chaoqiang.
Yang Xiaomei Jingjing, Yin Xin, Xie Lei, Ding Yongyan, Zuo Longqiang.
Zhang Menglian, Liang Xiaoxia, Li Jinxiao, Wang Jingru. Ding Zhiyuan, Dong Xiaoya, Zhang Tengyun.
He Guiling, Liu Youlin, Li Jiawei, Auspicious. Yin Zhifei, Jia Shuyi, Zhang Haifeng,
Vice director Ma Yunbo Zhang Yiyi
Vice-director, Wei Tianci.
Assistant editor Zhai Kai.
Photographer, Gao, Wei.
Lighter Wang Gujun
Recording instructor, Lim Xin.
Team leader, Guo Baojun.
Liu Shusen, deputy team leader.
The team leader, Wang Qitao.
Ma Yulong.
Vice-captain of props, Liu Junqing.
Production Deputy Director Yu Haitao
to lead Su Kewen
Liang Ting Hui.
[Sun Tianyong]
Drama Producer Yang Haiqun Zhu
Legal consultant, Sun Shouheng.
Translator Qian Lei, Luo Yu E.
script planner, Wu Tian.
Manager Wang Kang Ning.
pilot Lauson Sky. Hart.
Pilot C-46, Geffon. David Blue.
Charles Michelle Demson. Aldride.
Japanese commander, Teishi. Mizuno.
Spanis Jeff. Respector.
Marshal. Watson.
I'm a Japanese officer, Takasaki YAM.
Alexander, Ko Sia, Kevin. Joy.
Colonel Kubo P.J.Marino America.
Preparation pilot Kuri Aron. Wilton.
Staff table.
Director assistant Luis. Feeling Delgado.
The drama Cherry Su
Martial arts team.
The martial arts director, Liu Jie.
Actor assistant director Go Haesan
Photographer Lee Moon Ho.
Recording assistant Liu Xingxing Cao Mengchao
Lee Seong-ha.
Hwan-ha.
Music editor Dai Tingting Liu Zongyun
Music Producer Kun Music Studio
Recorder John Kurrander.
Music coordination Zhang Xiaoming and Qiu Yunbing
Theme Song: "The Moon Open Eyes".
How bright the performance is.
Recording/mix Tong Xinyu
Producer Liu Jingjing Liu Xuandou
Producer Liu Jing Yang Yu
Lyrics: Zhao Jun, Zhang Jingyi
Composition/Arrangement Wang Tianjin
Late production.
Peking Pei Hua Culture Co., Ltd.
Project Manager Wang Yiwei.
Environmental Effect Editor Wang Ke Yu Jiang Ji Yu Lau.
Special Effect Editor Wang Yangbing Wang Hawk
Full-range recording, Wang, go.
Color Li Yang.
Narrator white horse.
Japanese voice tutor Qian Lei
Voice actor Takahashi Ching-hwi
Video Director, list Jia.
Video director Liu Bing
Model team leader Fan Haowei
Lu Haowei.
The documentary
Chief Editor, Mjurlei.
Li Siying.
Legend Paradise on the Hai of Guangjiang, Guangjiang, Guangzhou and Guangzhou.
Guangzhou’s Tourism Center
Guangdong Kaiping Ping Building Tourism Development Co., Ltd.
Guangzhou Shawan Ancient Town Tourism Development Co., Ltd.
Zhongshan Film and TV City Co., Ltd.
New film and television Project Studio.
Beijing Huixin Yijie Movie Planning Co., Ltd.
Costume sponsor = Jiangsu Qianyu Environmental Engineering Co., Ltd.